<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Winter Cove Foundation</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Winter Cove Foundation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Winter Cove Foundation, started by Lewis Levin, is a private foundation and registered 501 (c) (3) tax-exempt, non-profit organization. The foundation focuses on organizations and projects that strive to improve tolerance in the face of inter-group tension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grantees</title>
      <link>/post/grantees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/grantees/</guid>
      <description>Past and present grantees of Winter Cove Foundation include:
 Recovery Cafe for the support of marginalized people who may suffer addiction, abuse, or homelessness; College Possible to enable lower income students from public schools to attend college at rates equal to or greater than their more affluent peers; Plymouth Housing seeking to reduce homelessness by providing safe, comfortable and longterm housing for disabled people, low wage working people, and struggling veterans; Ashesi University providing world class college education to Africans who stay in Africa to fill leadership positions in business, not-for-profit service organizations, and government; New Israel Fund to help defend and build civic organizations that enhance democracy in Israel or that defend the civil rights of disadvantaged groups in Israel; International Planned Parenthood Foundation to provide pregnancy counseling, birth control, and abortion services to women struggling to manage the wellbeing of their families; FareStart and Food Lifeline to provide food and jobs to people struggling with economic challenges and food insecurity;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission</title>
      <link>/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mission/</guid>
      <description>The mission of Winter Cove foundation is to:  Support programs and research that improve conditions for greater tolerance among diverse religious, ethnic, socio-economic, or cultural communities; Support original research in the field where intolerance conflicts are occurring to experiment with practical approaches to mitigate tensions between diverse ethnic and cultural communities; Explore and clarify principles that help make it possible for multi-ethnic societies to function successfully.  Winter Cove makes donations to other charitable organizations including educational and cultural institutions and organizations consistent with mission of the foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
